I am here today to show you how to make quick and easy Spanish recipes.
Over in this pot we have finished our quick and easy Spanish style chicken and sausage and see how it has got this nice sauce dripping down and the peas are still green and everything.
We need something to sop up that sauce.
Over here I have got some onion that I am just going to throw into the food processor and a little garlic, we are going to see if we can get that out of the head.
This is always a problem.
It never wants to work with me, never ever, like now.
One clove of garlic and over in the hot pan we have got some oil heating, just a little vegetable oil.
You can use olive oil, which is what I usually use but we do not want to overpower our flavor so we are just going to stick with the vegetable oil.
Just give it a nice mince, nice and fine and small and you know that they are minced whenever it starts pulling away from the middle and starts spreading out to the sides.
Just like that now.
Put this into the pot, because it has to sizzle a little and it starts cooking immediately and just like that we have the beginnings of our beautiful yellow rice.